{"entrance":{"x":1,"y":19,"angle":270},"exit":{"x":5,"y":1},"grid":[[{"x":0,"y":0,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":0,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":0,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":0,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_18","left":"walls_1_18","back":"walls_1_18","right":"walls_1_18","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_18","left":"walls_1_18","back":"walls_1_18","right":"walls_1_18","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_18","left":"walls_1_18","back":"walls_1_18","right":"walls_1_18","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":0,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":10,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":17,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":18,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":21,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":25,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_17","left":"walls_1_17","back":"walls_1_17","right":"walls_1_17","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_17","left":"walls_1_17","back":"walls_1_17","right":"walls_1_17","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":12,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":19,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":20,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":21,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":22,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":2,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_06","left":"doors_1_06","back":"doors_1_06","right":"doors_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":2,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_06","left":"walls_1_06","back":"walls_1_06","right":"walls_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_06","left":"walls_1_06","back":"walls_1_06","right":"walls_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":17,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":19,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":20,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":21,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":19,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":20,"y":3,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_03","left":"doors_1_03","back":"doors_1_03","right":"doors_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"key":"yellow"},{"x":21,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":22,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":true},{"x":25,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":16,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":17,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":18,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":24,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":21,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":5,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":true},{"x":3,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":6,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_05","left":"doors_1_05","back":"doors_1_05","right":"doors_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"key":"red"},{"x":6,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":21,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":8,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":12,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_06","left":"walls_1_06","back":"walls_1_06","right":"walls_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":7,"door":true,"axis":"y","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":19,"y":7,"door":true,"axis":"y","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":22,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":25,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":21,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":11,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":11,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}}],[{"x":0,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_06","left":"walls_1_06","back":"walls_1_06","right":"walls_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":25,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":9,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":10,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":11,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":3,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":12,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":21,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":23,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":15,"door":true,"axis":"y","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":12,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_06","left":"walls_1_06","back":"walls_1_06","right":"walls_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":10,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":11,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":12,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":13,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":14,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":15,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":16,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":17,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":18,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":23,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":17,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":17,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":17,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":17,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":17,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":9,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":10,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":11,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":17,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":18,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":17,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":21,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"},"axis":"x","pushable":true},{"x":25,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":18,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":9,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":10,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":11,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":12,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":13,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":14,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":15,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":16,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":17,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_02","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":18,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":19,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_12","left":"walls_1_12","back":"walls_1_12","right":"walls_1_12","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":21,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":24,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_17","left":"walls_1_17","back":"walls_1_17","right":"walls_1_17","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":19,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_17","left":"walls_1_17","back":"walls_1_17","right":"walls_1_17","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":10,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":17,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":18,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":19,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_11","left":"walls_1_11","back":"walls_1_11","right":"walls_1_11","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":20,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":21,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_10","left":"walls_1_10","back":"walls_1_10","right":"walls_1_10","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":22,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":23,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":19,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":25,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}],[{"x":0,"y":20,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_18","left":"walls_1_18","back":"walls_1_18","right":"walls_1_18","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":1,"y":20,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_18","left":"walls_1_18","back":"walls_1_18","right":"walls_1_18","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":20,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_18","left":"walls_1_18","back":"walls_1_18","right":"walls_1_18","bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":4,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":5,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":6,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":7,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":8,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":9,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":10,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":11,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":12,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":13,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":14,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":15,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":16,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":17,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":18,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":19,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":20,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":21,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":22,"y":20,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":23,"y":20,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":24,"y":20,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":25,"y":20,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false}]],"objects":[{"x":12,"y":2,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":15,"y":2,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":18,"y":2,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":4,"y":3,"name":"blue_torch","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.1875,"length":0.1875,"height":0.546875},{"x":6,"y":3,"name":"blue_torch","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.1875,"length":0.1875,"height":0.546875},{"x":8,"y":3,"name":"static_objects_1_01","blocking":true,"width":0.328125,"length":0.328125,"height":1},{"x":10,"y":3,"name":"static_objects_1_01","blocking":true,"width":0.328125,"length":0.328125,"height":1},{"x":12,"y":3,"name":"static_objects_1_02","blocking":true,"width":0.375,"length":0.375,"height":0.453125},{"x":5,"y":4,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":9,"y":4,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":13,"y":5,"name":"static_objects_1_02","blocking":true,"width":0.375,"length":0.375,"height":0.453125},{"x":15,"y":5,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":24,"y":6,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":5,"y":7,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":14,"y":7,"name":"explosive_barrel","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.40625,"length":0.40625,"height":0.515625},{"x":21,"y":7,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":2,"y":8,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":9,"y":8,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":13,"y":8,"name":"static_objects_1_04","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.640625},{"x":10,"y":9,"name":"blue_torch","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.1875,"length":0.1875,"height":0.546875},{"x":16,"y":9,"name":"static_objects_1_02","blocking":true,"width":0.375,"length":0.375,"height":0.453125},{"x":24,"y":9,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":15,"y":10,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":17,"y":10,"name":"static_objects_1_06","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.5625},{"x":2,"y":11,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":6,"y":11,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":9,"y":11,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":4,"y":12,"name":"explosive_barrel","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.40625,"length":0.40625,"height":0.515625},{"x":10,"y":12,"name":"blue_torch","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.1875,"length":0.1875,"height":0.546875},{"x":17,"y":12,"name":"static_objects_1_06","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.5625},{"x":24,"y":13,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":5,"y":14,"name":"static_objects_1_01","blocking":true,"width":0.328125,"length":0.328125,"height":1},{"x":5,"y":15,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":9,"y":15,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":13,"y":15,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":14,"y":15,"name":"explosive_barrel","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.40625,"length":0.40625,"height":0.515625},{"x":17,"y":15,"name":"static_objects_1_06","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.5625},{"x":2,"y":16,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":12,"y":16,"name":"static_objects_1_04","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.640625},{"x":5,"y":18,"name":"static_objects_1_01","blocking":true,"width":0.328125,"length":0.328125,"height":1},{"x":11,"y":18,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":15,"y":18,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":17,"y":18,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125}],"items":[{"amount":50,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"chaingun","x":15,"y":1,"name":"items_07"},{"amount":50,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"chaingun","x":23,"y":2,"name":"items_07"},{"color":"red","type":"keyitem","x":1,"y":3,"name":"items_04"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"chaingun","x":21,"y":4,"name":"items_11"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"launcher","x":9,"y":6,"name":"items_12"},{"amount":20,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":12,"y":6,"name":"items_06"},{"amount":25,"type":"healthitem","x":6,"y":7,"name":"items_14"},{"amount":20,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":18,"y":7,"name":"items_06"},{"amount":10,"type":"healthitem","x":22,"y":7,"name":"items_13"},{"amount":10,"type":"healthitem","x":2,"y":12,"name":"items_13"},{"amount":20,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":19,"y":12,"name":"items_06"},{"amount":15,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"pistol","x":5,"y":15,"name":"items_05"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":9,"y":15,"name":"items_10"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"pistol","x":2,"y":16,"name":"items_09"},{"amount":10,"type":"healthitem","x":8,"y":18,"name":"items_13"},{"color":"yellow","type":"keyitem","x":9,"y":18,"name":"items_02"},{"amount":50,"type":"healthitem","x":13,"y":18,"name":"items_15"},{"amount":50,"type":"healthitem","x":21,"y":18,"name":"items_15"},{"amount":20,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":22,"y":18,"name":"items_06"}],"enemies":[{"x":10,"y":1,"name":"demon","proneHeight":7,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.578125},{"x":11,"y":1,"name":"soul","float":true,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.53125},{"x":16,"y":1,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":20,"y":1,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":13,"y":2,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":18,"y":2,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":5,"y":3,"name":"cacodemon","float":true,"proneHeight":10,"width":0.734375,"length":0.734375,"height":0.734375},{"x":15,"y":3,"name":"imp","proneHeight":5,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625},{"x":20,"y":4,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":4,"y":5,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":6,"y":5,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":15,"y":5,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":24,"y":5,"name":"demon","proneHeight":7,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.578125},{"x":13,"y":6,"name":"demon","proneHeight":7,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.578125},{"x":22,"y":6,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":2,"y":7,"name":"soul","float":true,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.53125},{"x":4,"y":7,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":21,"y":7,"name":"demon","proneHeight":7,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.578125},{"x":14,"y":8,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":22,"y":8,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":2,"y":9,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":9,"y":9,"name":"cacodemon","float":true,"proneHeight":10,"width":0.734375,"length":0.734375,"height":0.734375},{"x":10,"y":10,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":15,"y":10,"name":"imp","proneHeight":5,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625},{"x":22,"y":10,"name":"imp","proneHeight":5,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625},{"x":3,"y":11,"name":"demon","proneHeight":7,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.578125},{"x":5,"y":12,"name":"sergeant","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":9,"y":12,"name":"imp","proneHeight":5,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625},{"x":16,"y":12,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":23,"y":13,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":17,"y":14,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":11,"y":15,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":15,"y":16,"name":"soul","float":true,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.53125},{"x":20,"y":16,"name":"cacodemon","float":true,"proneHeight":10,"width":0.734375,"length":0.734375,"height":0.734375},{"x":23,"y":16,"name":"imp","proneHeight":5,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625},{"x":5,"y":17,"name":"trooper","proneHeight":5,"width":0.46875,"length":0.46875,"height":0.625},{"x":12,"y":18,"name":"demon","proneHeight":7,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.578125},{"x":17,"y":18,"name":"imp","proneHeight":5,"width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625}]}